[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Condoleezza Rice, is it more fun being in power or is it more fun after power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Well it's certainly different being out of power.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Condoleezza Rice"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "But in practical reality what can you now do you couldn't do, that you missed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, it's less of what I can do now that I couldn't do then than -- there isn't the sort of relentlessness of the days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams that one day you'd be in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well I was going to be a concert pianist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Because you're a mad football nut, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "I'm a mad football --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What values did they give you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, that was what was extraordinary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "And why would you convince yourself that you had done this terrible, God-forsaken job?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "ICE: Well, because there's no greater challenge and there is no greater honor than to be in public service.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "You're not far off, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Well no, I'm -- I'm pretty far from that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Anything you want to share with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Nothing but a sniffle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Well, not a sniffle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 190, "question": "How?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "And I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 192, "question": "How -- how do you stop getting a cold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, you --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "ICE: You don't get colds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Keeping fit -- did you drink alcohol when you were in office?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Well, occasionally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Did you drink alcohol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Sure, occasionally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "-- can you ever actually get intoxicated?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Of course not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Are you still absurdly fit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "I'm still fit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Every day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Why do you do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Because I like to exercise in the morning and I like to have the whole day before me after I exercise.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "How -- how long do you do it for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "About an hour.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Pump weights?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "I do cardio.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Kick boxing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "I do some kick boxing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Who do you think of when you're smashing the -- the bag?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I don't think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Do you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Hmm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Birmingham"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "It must be a great sadness, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, I have to -- first of all, Birmingham was not an easy place grow up if you were black, but I was fortunate to live in a very loving family, very loving community.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Did he make you tough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, certainly, I think I had -- I have, perhaps part of my father's personality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2000"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "What would he have made of what happened to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Well, he knew a little bit because he died in 2000.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "She'd been amazed, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Well I think she would have been amazed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "What kind of woman was she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "My mom was a lady in the nicest sense of the term.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "To use the language of the gun in --in that kind of way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Well, the fact is that our politics is pretty rough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "But should it -- should it be that rough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "-- experienced it myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What about towards -- what about towards opponents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNS", ":", "WP", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, let me just say -- all of that said, I would like to see the politics cool down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "How's President Obama doing, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, I'm very fond of the president personally.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "But could you have been tempted, do you think, in other circumstances, to vote for President Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Well, I think that he is a fine person and he's doing his best for this country and I was personally quite gratified that America elected a black president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Would you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "He doesn't need me in his administration.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Hypothetically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I don't do hypothetical, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Would you -- would you join the Tea Party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, let me -- let me finish with the --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "Because if -- if your party gets split by her and the Tea Party, isn't that a big problem for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Well, there's a long logic chain there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Could you win with her do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I -- I have no -- I do international politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "-- you're not fearful of that candidate being Sarah Palin?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I -- I'm not fearful of the -- the candidates that are on the horizon.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "But you can't ever win a war on terror, can you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Of course you can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September 11th"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "How?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "You can win this war against the extremist who did what they did to us on September 11th.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Are we winning the war in Afghanistan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "I do think we're winning the war in Afghanistan, but it's very, very slow.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "I mean, is there not an absolutely obvious problem here, which is the moment you set a time table, the Taliban -- they know their terrain, they disappear, they regroup, they wait?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Well I don't like time tables, to be quite frank.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Afghanistan"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Does it worry your, as somebody who in terms of personal probity has never been questioned, a woman of integrity, that you're doing business with President Karzai, who most people would say on the ground is, you know, borderline corrupt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "RBS", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "There's a lot of corruption in Afghanistan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Karzai"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ":", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Would that concern you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Of course -- of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "How do you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Well, the same set of circumstances may not lead you to the same set of tools.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "-- Ahmadinejad?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "ICE: Well I think he was certainly a very dangerous man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "IN", ":", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "If you were -- if you were still a secretary of state, and Saddam Hussein was still alive, you can't tell me now knowing what we know about all these countries, that you wouldn't be kept awake more by North Korea and Iran than you would by Iraq, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Oh, I would -- I would certainly -- kept -- well first of all, you don't have to make a choice.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Iraq"], "LOCATION": ["North Korea", "Iran"], "PERSON": ["Saddam Hussein"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Do you regret now using the weapons of mass destruction as a pretext of war?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Piers, the fact is that what you know today can affect what you do tomorrow, but not what you did yesterday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "You wouldn't dispute that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Well, I don't dispute that he didn't have stockpiles of weapons of mass destruction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "-- or would you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "No, I think the mistake -- and this was a mistake -- was to put a spotlight simply on the weapons of mass destruction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Saddam Hussein"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 647, "question": "That he was told to go and do this, and effectively sold the -- the reasons for this war on the evidence which actually turned out to be bogus?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Well, the reasons for this war, again, were that Saddam Hussein was a threat --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "But you're aware that there was a misconception by a number of Americans that Saddam must have been involved in 9-11?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "Of course, and it was a reasonable question to ask after 9-11.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "That is a price worth paying, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "Given the centrality of the Middle East to American security and to the security of the free world, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "How have you avoided being snared in the marital trap?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "Well, actually I live in California now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "How close have you come?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "I've come close.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "How many times?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I'm not going there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "Do you hold out hope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Did you dream of a fairy tale wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "You're quite a catch; aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "Well, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Are you romantic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 717, "question": "How does it manifest itself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "Well, I love romantic music and romantic movies and --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Are you -- are you high maintenance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "No, of course not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 747, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 748, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "You don't know what gumbo is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 756, "question": "Is it meat, fish, or is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 757, "answer": "It's -- it's seafood and sausage in a very, very thick sauce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Stanford Cardinals"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "So on this hypothetical date, I've had gumbo and I'd be watching which football team?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "WDT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "Uh, the Stanford Cardinals these days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "Not all night as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "ICE: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "I can imagine that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 799, "question": "What are you 30?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 800, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 801, "question": "Thirty-nine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 802, "answer": "We'll leave it at that .", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "That's not going to get your juices flowing, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "ICE: It's not going to get my juices flowing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Secretary of State"]}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "Playing -- oh, so you consider being a university professor little league; do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", ":", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "Compared to Secretary of State.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "The moment you'd relive again if you got the chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "Playing with Yo-Yo Ma.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 831, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 832, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]